A true tall tale.
Get Low is a drama, mystery, comedy film directed by Aaron Schneider.
A movie spun out of equal parts folk tale, fable and real-life legend about the mysterious,
1930s Tennessee hermit who famously threw his own rollicking funeral party...
while he was still alive.
Felix Bush, played by Robert Duvall.
Frank Quinn, played by Bill Murray.
Mattie Darrow, played by Sissy Spacek.
Buddy, played by Lucas Black.
Rev. Charlie Jackson, played by Bill Cobbs.
Rev. Gus Horton, played by Gerald McRaney.
Get Low is a 2009 drama film directed by Aaron Schneider,
and written by Chris Provenzano and C.
Gaby Mitchell.
It tells the story of a Tennessee hermit in the 1930s who
throws his own funeral party while still alive.
The film stars Robert Duvall, Bill Murray, Sissy Spacek and Lucas Black.
Duvall was awarded the Hollywood Film Festival Award
for Best Actor for his lead performance.
The film explores themes of hermit, tennessee, funeral director, 1930s.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional and mind_bending.